<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bhagvat Geeta App</string>
    <string-array name="chapters">
        <item>Chapter 1</item>
        <item>Chapter 2</item>
        <item>Chapter 3</item>
        <item>Chapter 4</item>
        <item>Chapter 5</item>
        <item>Chapter 6</item>
        <item>Chapter 7</item>
        <item>Chapter 8</item>
        <item>Chapter 9</item>
        <item>Chapter 10</item>
        <item>Chapter 11</item>
        <item>Chapter 12</item>
        <item>Chapter 13</item>
        <item>Chapter 14</item>
        <item>Chapter 15</item>
        <item>Chapter 16</item>
        <item>Chapter 17</item>
        <item>Chapter 18</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="_47">सञ्जय उवाच | एवमुक्त्वार्जुन: सङ्ख्ये रथोपस्थ उपाविशत् | विसृज्य सशरं चापं शोकसंविग्नमानस: || 47||</string>
    <string name="shlokName">अर्जुनविषादयोग</string>
    <string name="meaningText">"Whoever offers Me with devotion-a leaf, a flower, a fruit, or water, I accept that (gift) of the pure-hearted man which has been devotionally presented."</string>
    <string name="text">The seventh chapter of the Bhagavad Gita is \"Gyaan Vigyana Yoga \". In this chapter, Krishna reveals that he is the Supreme Truth, the principal cause and the sustaining force of everything. He reveals his illusionary energy in this material world called Maya, which is very difficult to overcome but those who surrender their minds unto Him attain Him easily. He also describes the four types of people who surrender to Him in devotion and the four kinds that do not. Krishna confirms that He is the Ultimate Reality and those who realize this Truth reach the pinnacle of spiritual realization and unite with the Lord.
</string>
    <string name="wordMeaning">"verseyaḥ—who; mām—me; ajam—unborn; anādim—beginningless; cha—and; vetti—know; loka—of the universe; mahā-īśhvaram—the Supreme Lord; asammūḍhaḥ—undeluded; saḥ—they; martyeṣhu—among mortals; sarva-pāpaiḥ—from all evils; pramuchyate—are freed from-3"</string>
    <string name="summary"><u>Summary</u></string>
    <string name="transliteration">buddhir jñānam asammohaḥ kṣhamā satyaṁ damaḥ śhamaḥ
sukhaṁ duḥkhaṁ bhavo ’bhāvo bhayaṁ chābhayameva cha
</string>
    <string name="decription">The first chapter of the Bhagavad Gita - \"Arjuna Vishada Yoga\" introduces the setup, the setting, the characters and the circumstances that led to the epic battle of Mahabharata, fought between the Pandavas and the Kauravas. It outlines the reasons that led to the revelation of the of Bhagavad Gita.\nAs both armies stand ready for the battle, the mighty warrior Arjuna, on observing the warriors on both sides becomes increasingly sad and depressed due to the fear of losing his relatives and friends and the consequent sins attributed to killing his own relatives. So, he surrenders to Lord Krishna, seeking a solution. Thus, follows the wisdom of the Bhagavad Gita."</string>
</resources>